Guide to the David Price Papers, 1960-2006 and undated RL.01048
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Congressional Papers Record Group, 1981-1994 and undated
  - Legislative Files Series, 1981-1994, bulk 1987-1994 and undated, 66 boxes
    - Ways and Means Subseries, 1984-1994 and undated
      - Appreciated Property (101-103), circa 1991 (Box CLE-53)
      - The Bubble, 1989 (Box CLE-53)
      - Burlington MSA [Metropolitan Statistical Area], 1990-1992 (Box CLE-53)
      - Black and Decker/G.E. [General Electric] Pensions, 1989 (Box CLE-53)
      - Cafeteria Plans, 1988 (Box CLE-53)
      - Capital Gains Tax, 1989-1991 (Box CLE-53)
      - Coast Guard Boat User Fees (102), 1991-1992 (Box CLE-53)
      - Common Funds (102), 1991 (Box CLE-53)
      - BTU Tax (103), 1993 (Box CLE-53)
      - Corporate Sponsorship (102), 1992 (Box CLE-53)
      - Daycare Providers Simplification (102), 1991 (Box CLE-53)
      - Earned Income Credit, 1990-1992 (Box CLE-53)
      - Economic Growth Package (102), 1991-1992 (Box CLE-53)
      - Employee Educational Assistance (102), 1990 (Box CLE-53)
      - Estate Freeze, 1989-1990 (Box CLE-53)
      - Ethanol Gas (101), 1990 and undated (Box CLE-53)
      - Fairness for Families (102), 1991-1992 (Box CLE-53)
      - HR 2106/Family Caregivers (102), 1991 (Box CLE-53)
      - Farmer Cooperatives (101-103), 1991-1992 and undated (Box CLE-53)
      - Farmers Withholding Tax (101), undated (Box CLE-53)
      - FICA Tax Repeal (102), 1991 (Box CLE-53)
      - Food Bank Donations (100), 1988 (Box CLE-53)
      - Football Coaches (100), 1987 (Box CLE-53)
      - Gas Excise Tax (100-102), 1988-1990 (Box CLE-53)
      - Gramm-Rudman, 1985-1989 (Oversize-box OVSZ 1)
      - High-Speed Rail Bonds (102), 1992 (Box CLE-53)
      - Holly Farms/Tyson Transfer, 1990 (Box CLE-53)
      - Homebuyers Tax Credit (102), 1992 (Box CLE-53)
      - Hurricane Hugo/Timber Tax Relief (101), 1990 (Box CLE-53)
      - Imputed Interest/Carolina Meadows, 1989 (Box CLE-53)
      - Imputed Interest/Springmoor, 1984-1992 (Box CLE-53)
      - Intangibles Amortization (102), 1991 (Box CLE-54)
      - Investment Tax Credit, 1991 (Box CLE-54)
      - IRAs [Individual Retirement Accounts] (102), 1991 (Box CLE-54)
      - Iraqi Aggression Tax (102), 1990 (Box CLE-54)
      - Leveraged Buyouts/General, 1988-1989 (Box CLE-54)
      - HR 134/Living Benefit Bill (102), 1991 (Box CLE-54)
      - Low-Income Housing Credit (102), 1991 (Box CLE-54)
      - Luxury Taxes (102), 1991-1992 (Box CLE-54)
      - Mail Order Sales Tax (101-103), 1988-1992 (Box CLE-54)
      - Military and Taxes (102), 1990-1991 (Box CLE-54)
      - Taxation/Nonelective Benefits (101), 1987-1988 and undated (Box CLE-54)
      - Passive Activity Loss (101-102), 1991-1992 (Box CLE-54)
      - Non-Profit 401(K) Plans (101-103), 1989 (Box CLE-54)
      - OMB/CBO [Office of Management and Budget/Congressional Budget Office] Scorekeeping (102), 1991 (Box CLE-54)
      - Pension/General, 1991-1992 (Box CLE-54)
      - Pension Simplification (102), 1991 (Box CLE-54)
      - Railroad Retirement, 1990 and undated (Box CLE-54)
      - R and E [Research and Experimentation] Tax Credit (102), 1991 (Box CLE-54)
      - Revenue Foregone (103), 1993 (Box CLE-54)
      - Section 89 (101), 1989 (Box CLE-54)
      - Self-Employed/Health Deductions (101-102), 1989-1991 (Box CLE-54)
      - SOT [Special Occupational Taxes] (102), 1990-1992 (Box CLE-54)
      - HR 4408-Small Issue Industrial Bonds (101 and 102), 1990-1992 (Box CLE-54)
      - Source Taxes (102), 1991 (Box CLE-54)
      - Square D Pension, 1991 (Box CLE-54)
      - Student Loan Bill (103), 1991-1993 (Box CLE-54)
      - Student Loan Deferral (102), 1990-1991 (Box CLE-54)
      - Student Loans/David's Bill (100-102), 1987-1992 (Box CLE-54)
      - Targeted Jobs Tax Credit (102), 1991 (Box CLE-54)
      - Taxation/Retirement Income, 1989 (Box CLE-54)
      - Taxpayers Bill of Rights, 1988 and undated (Box CLE-54)
      - Tax Exempt Bond Simplification, 1989-1990 (Box CLE-54)
      - Tax Extenders (102), 1991-1992 (Box CLE-54)
      - Tax Fairness (102), 1990-1992 (Box CLE-54)
      - HR 5011/Tax Improvement Act (102), 1992 (Box CLE-54)
      - Tax Reform Act of 1986, 1986 (Box CLE-54)
      - Technical Corrections Act (1988), 1988 (Box CLE-54)
      - Tobacco Taxes-General, 1989 (Box CLE-54)
      - Transit Tax Equity, 1991 and undated (Box CLE-54)
      - UBIT [Unrelated Business Income Tax]-General, 1987-1989 (Box CLE-55)
      - Utilities Ratepayer Refund (101), 1987-1989 (Box CLE-55)
      - Unemployment Compensation (102), 1991-1992 (Box CLE-55)
      - Unemployment Compensation Reform, 1992 (Box CLE-55)
      - Urban Aid Packaging/HR 11 (102), 1992 (Box CLE-55)
      - VAT [Value-Added Tax] Tax, 1992 (Box CLE-55)
      - HR 2629/Women's Business Development (102), 1991 (Box CLE-55)
      - Trade Issues-General, 1991 and undated (Box CLE-55)
      - Miscellaneous Trade Letters/Administration (103), 1993-1994 (Box CLE-55)
      - Miscellaneous Letters to Administration (102), 1990-1993 (Box CLE-55)
      - H. Con. Res. 246 (102), 1992 (Box CLE-55)
      - Ajinomoto/Amino Acid Tariffs, 1990 (Box CLE-55)
      - Breast Cancer Duty Suspend (103), 1993 (Box CLE-55)
      - Caribbean Basin/Trade (101), 1989 (Box CLE-55)
      - Caribbean Basic Caucus (Box CLE-55)
      - Ceramic Tile, 1990-1992 (Box CLE-55)
      - Project-Fish Nets/Don Betts, 1988-1994 (Box CLE-55)
      - MFN [Most Favored Nation]/China (103), 1993-1994 (Box CLE-55)
      - MFN Status/China (101), undated (Box CLE-55)
      - MFN Status/China (102 (1st)), undated (Box CLE-55)
      - GATT [General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade]
        - Letters to Administration (103), 1993-1994 (Box CLE-55)
        - Admin. and M.C.S. (103), 1994 (Box CLE-55)
        - Letters, 1992-1994 (Box CLE-55)
        - CRS and Reports (103), circa 1993-1994 (Box CLE-55)
        - Textiles (103), 1993-1994 (Box CLE-55)
        - Miscellaneous (103), 1994 (Box CLE-55)
        - (102), 1989-1994 (Box CLE-55)
        - Oil Seeds, 1992 (Box CLE-55)
      - MFN China (HR 2212)(102 (2nd)), 1992 (Box CLE-55)
      - Export Administration Act (103), 1994 (Box CLE-55)
      - Footwear/UNICOR and Military (101), 1990 (Box CLE-55)
      - Foreign Ownership (101), 1989 (Box CLE-55)
      - Glaxo-Duty Suspensions (102), 1992 (Box CLE-55)
      - General System Preferences (103), undated (Box CLE-55)
      - Gerber and Guatemala (103), 1994 (Box CLE-55)
      - Glaxo/Duty Suspend. Bills (103), undated (Box CLE-55)
      - Glaxo/Ranitidine Hydrochloride, 1990-1992 (Box CLE-55)
      - Hosiery Knitting Machines/Duty Suspension (103), 1993 (Box CLE-55)
      - Hosiery Manufacturers, 1992 (Box CLE-56)
      - Japan-Super 301, 1990-1991 (Box CLE-56)
      - U.S.-Japan Trade Relations, 1989 (Box CLE-56)
      - Lumber-Canada (101), 1992 (Box CLE-56)
      - Mallinckrodt-Foreign Trade Subzone, 1990 (Box CLE-56)
      - Miscellaneous Tariff Act (102), 1992 (Box CLE-56)
      - N.C. and Trade, 1990s (Box CLE-56)
      - N.C. District Export Council, 1987 (Box CLE-56)
      - NAFTA [North American Free Trade Agreement]
        - Articles (103), 1993 (Box CLE-56)
        - Since Enactment, 1994 (Box CLE-56)
        - Jobs, Labor, etc., 1993 (Box CLE-56)
        - Economic Studies (103), 1993 and undated (Box CLE-56)
        - Administration (103), 1993 (Box CLE-56)
        - Environment (103), 1993 (Box CLE-56)
        - Foreign Policy (103), 1993 (Box CLE-56)
        - Groups Con (103), 1993 (Box CLE-56)
        - Groups Pro (103), 1993 (Box CLE-56)
        - Miscellaneous Concerns, 1993 (Box CLE-56)
        - N.C., 1993 (Box CLE-56)
        - Textiles (103), 1993 (Box CLE-56)
        - Thank Yous, 1993-1994 (Box CLE-56)
        - Final-General (102), 1990-1992 (Box CLE-56)
      - HR 2056/Shipbuilding Trade (102), 1992 (Box CLE-56)
      - Soda Ash, 1991 (Box CLE-56)
      - Textiles-General, 1991-1993 (Box CLE-56)
      - 1990 Textile Bill (101), 1990 (Box CLE-56)
      - Textile Bill (100), 1987-1988 (Box CLE-56)
      - Textile Machinery Modernization Act (103), 1994 and undated (Box CLE-56)
      - Textile Machinery Bill (101), 1989-1991 (Box CLE-56)
      - Trade Expansion Act (102), 1992 (Box CLE-56)
      - Wire Rope Dumping (102), 1992 (Box CLE-56)
      - S.S. [Social Security]/General, undated (Box CLE-56)
      - S.S. Earnings Test (101), undated (Box CLE-56)
      - HR 2766/Life Insurance Agents (102), 1991-1992 (Box CLE-56)
      - SSI, 1990 and undated (Box CLE-56)
      - Moynihan's S.S. Payroll Tax Cut (101), 1990-1991 (Box CLE-56)
      - Social Security Notch, 1988-1992 (Box CLE-56)
      - Notch Follow-Up, 1988 and undated (Box CLE-56)
      - Welfare Reform (103), 1994 (Box CLE-56)
    - Commemorative Legislation Subseries, 1991-1994
      Consists primarily of copies of correspondence, usually requesting Price to cosponsor commemorative legislation, and his positive responses. These letters discuss legislation designating certain calendar days as commemorative, designed to raise awareness for a particular medical condition or gain recognition for a cause or particular group or people (e.g. Emergency Services Week). There is frequently a note appended where Price (or a member of his staff) indicated his reason for cosponsoring and staff input. Correspondents are usually congressional colleagues with whom the legislation originated. In rough chronological order as received.
      - Commemoratives 102nd [Congress], 1991-1992, 4 folders (Box CLE-57)
      - Commemoratives 103rd [Congress], 1993-1994, 3 folders (Box CLE-57)
    - Cosigned Letters Subseries, 1987-1994
      Consists almost entirely of correspondence, usually sent between House Members, the Speaker of the House, or sometimes the President or an outside party. The letters relate to a variety of matters, political causes, legislative initiatives, all attempting to influence policy and legislation. All are letters for which multiple cosigners were sought, including Price. The file appears to be one of record for Price, although his signature was not confirmed on each letter. Arranged by Congress and sometimes further arranged by topic (House committee areas of jurisdiction).
      - Cosigned 100th [Congress], 1987-1988 (Box CLE-57)
      - Cosigned 101st
        - Agriculture-Banking, 1989-1990 (Box CLE-57)
        - Budget, 1989-1990 (Box CLE-58)
        - Education/Labor-Foreign Affairs, 1989-1990 (Box CLE-58)
        - Foreign Affairs, 1989-1990 (Box CLE-58)
        - Government Operations-Judiciary, 1989-1990 (Box CLE-58)
        - Merchant Marines-Ways and Means, 1989-1990 (Box CLE-58)
      - Cosigned 102nd, 1991-1992, 2 folders (Box CLE-58)
      - Cosigned 103rd, Part I, 1993-1994, 2 folders (Box CLE-58)
      - Cosigned 103rd, Part II, 1993-1994, 2 folders (Box CLE-59)
    - Cosponsorship Files Subseries, 1987-1994
      Incoming letters, mostly from congressional colleagues, asking Price to cosponsor legislation, and Price's positive responses. Briefing memos, correspondence, and staff comments are often included. Arranged by Congress.
      - Cosponsorships 100th, 1987-1988, 4 folders (Box CLE-59)
      - Cosponsorships 101st, Part I, 1988-1990, 2 folders (Box CLE-59)
      - Cosponsorships 101st, Parts II-V, 1988-1990, 8 folders (Box CLE-60)
      - Cosponsorships 102nd, 1991-1992, 5 folders (Box CLE-61)
      - Cosponsorships 103rd, 1993-1994, 1-2 of 4 folders (Box CLE-61)
      - Cosponsorships 103rd, 1993-1994, 3-4 of 4 folders (Box CLE-61)
    - Standard Response Files Subseries, 1987-1994
      Contain standard form paragraphs on a particular topic that Price included in response to constituent/issue mail. These are sometimes referred to as "Library of Form Paragraphs." Constituents identified as being interested in a particular legislative area would be given a code identifying them to receive occasional legislative updates for that issue. Information on these issue codes is found in the first folder of the series. There are also other memos and documents relating to mass mailings.
      Arranged by Congress and then by House committee area. See also the Constituent Service Files.
      - Miscellaneous Constituent Coding, 1989-1994 (Box CLE-62)
      - Standard Responses 100th, #1-#5, 1987-1988, 5 folders (Box CLE-62)
      - Standard Responses 101st, #1-#3, 1988-1990, 3 folders (Box CLE-62)
      - Standard Responses 102nd, Pre-New Computer System, 1991 (Box CLE-62)
      - Standard Responses 102nd, Index, 1993 (Box CLE-63)
      - Standard Responses 102nd, #1-#5, 1991-1992 and undated, 5 folders (Box CLE-63)
      - Standard Responses 103rd, #1-#4, 1993-1994, 4 folders (Box CLE-63)
      - Standard Responses 103rd, #5, 1993-1994 (Box CLE-64)
      - Standard Response Enclosures, 1987-1992 (Box CLE-64)
      - Enclosures, 103rd, 1990-1994 (Box CLE-64)
    - Targeted Mail Subseries, 1989-1994
      Contains copies of letters sent to specific constituents. Handwritten codes assigned to each letter by Price's office identify particular policy areas, or some other identification of interest. Arranged by Congressional session then by topic.
      - Targeted Mail 100th-102nd, #1-#3, 1989-1992 (Box CLE-64)
      - Targeted Mail 103rd Congress, 1993-1994 (Box CLE-64)
      - Profiles-Database Printout, 103rd Congress, 1993-1994, 1 of 7 folders (Box CLE-64)
      - Profiles-Database Printout, 103rd Congress, 1993-1994, 2-7 of 7 folders (Box CLE-65)
    - Vote Files Subseries, 1987-1994
      Contains copies of pages from the Congressional Quarterly. Each contains short annotations on pieces of legislation and then a table indicating how certain members voted. Handwritten notes and marginalia indicate how Price voted on each bill as well as what appear to be the North Carolina delegation's vote tallies. 1988, 1989, and 1990 are the only years that also have database printouts with similar information; within each year, these printouts are further arranged by topic. Arranged by year.
      - Votes, 1987 (Box CLE-65)
      - Votes, 1988 (Box CLE-65)
      - Votes Parts I and II, 1988, 4 folders (Box CLE-66)
      - Votes [I] and [II], 1989, 2 folders (Box CLE-66)
      - Votes [I] and [II], 1990, 2 folders (Box CLE-66)
      - Votes, 1991 (Box CLE-67)
      - Votes, 1992 (Box CLE-67)
      - Votes, 1993, 2 folders (Box CLE-67)
      - Votes, 1994 (Box CLE-67)
  - Constituent Service Files Series, 1992-1994, 5 boxes
    - Issue Mail Subseries, 1992-1994
      Appears to be a representative sampling of constituent letters with Price's responses, documenting the North Carolina constituency's interest in and opinions on a variety of issues and Price's manner in handling comments and requests. Some clippings and other enclosures are also included. Topics vary but include gays in the military, health care reform, reproductive rights, and funding for the Environmental Protection Agency. Files are arranged by year, then alphabetically by constituent last name.
      - Miscellaneous Democratic Agenda/Constituent Mail Responses, 1990-1991 (Box CLE-67)
      - A-C, 1992, 3 folders (Box CLE-67)
      - D-R, 1992, 16 folders (Box CLE-68)
      - S-Z, 1992, 7 folders (Box CLE-69)
      - A-I, 1993, 10 folders (Box CLE-69)
      - J-Z, 1993, 14 folders (Box CLE-70)
      - A-C, 1994, 3 folders (Box CLE-70)
      - D-Z, 1994, 20 folders (Box CLE-71)
  - Press/Media Files Series, 1986-1994 and undated, 36 boxes
    - Public Files Subseries, 1986-1994
      Contains public information put out by Price or his office such as "welcome" letters to new constituents, many speeches including parts of the Congressional Record, committee or hearing testimony, targeted mailings, and event flyers. At least one speech in the Public Files was not composed or presented by Price, but by Lech Walesa. A partial index in the first folder lists some of the items by date (December 3, 1986 through June 29, 1992). Folder titles are transcribed directly from the original folders and contain many initialisms and acronyms; the most frequent are "CR" for the Congressional Record, "TM" for "targeted mailing," and "Enc./Encl." for "enclosure." Arranged in roughly in reverse chronological order.
      - Public File Index - Partial, 1986-1992 (Box CPM-1)
      - Floor Statement-GATT [General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade], 1994 Nov. 29 (Box CPM-1)
      - Keynote-Southern Public Radio Annual Conference, 1994 Nov. 19 (Box CPM-1)
      - Talking Points-7th Annual Congressional Veterans' Conference-Raleigh, 1994 Nov. 12 (Box CPM-1)
      - Remarks to Coastal Federal Credit Union, 1994 Oct. 25 (Box CPM-1)
      - Triangle Area Research Director's Club-Talking Points, 1994 Oct. 18 (Box CPM-1)
      - Speech, Alumni of Police Managers, re: Crime Bill, 1994 Oct. 14 (Box CPM-1)
      - Triangle Mortgage Bankers Association, 1994 Oct. 13 (Box CPM-1)
      - Floor Statement-National Day of Remembrance for Victims of Domestic Abuse, 1994 Oct. 4 (Box CPM-1)
      - Remarks: Grand Opening, Carrboro Health Center, 1994 Oct. 2 (Box CPM-1)
      - Transportation Trades, 1994 Sept. 28 (Box CPM-1)
      - CR-Trans Apps, 1994 Sept. 28 (Box CPM-1)
      - Statement, Orange-Durham Coalition for Battered Women Grant Announcement, 1994 Sept. 26 (Box CPM-1)
      - Dear Colleague-Congressional Fellows (Horn/Price), 1994 Sept. 20 (Box CPM-1)
      - Press Conference-N.C. Medical Society (Violence Against Women), 1994 Sept. 19 (Box CPM-1)
      - N.C. Rural Development Capital Access Program Kickoff Remarks, 1994 Sept. 16 (Box CPM-1)
      - Remarks-Dedication Ceremony-NCSU [North Carolina State University] Research Bldg. III, 1994 Sept. 14 (Box CPM-1)
      - Article- N.C. Medical Journal-Domestic Violence, 1994 Sept. (Box CPM-1)
      - Remarks-SE Storm Consortium Grant Announcement, 1994 Aug. 25 (Box CPM-1)
      - Floor Statement-re: Penny-Kasich-Stenholm Substitute Amendment, 1994 Aug. 12 (Box CPM-1)
      - Floor Remarks-Diabetes and Health Care Reform, 1994 Aug. 2 (Box CPM-1)
      - Press Conference Remarks-Crime Bill, 1994 Aug. 1 (Box CPM-1)
      - Speech-Woodrow Wilson Center for International Studies- Congressional Government Revisited, 1994 July 25 (Box CPM-1)
      - Floor Remarks-Tribute to Avery Upchurch, 1994 July 21 (Box CPM-1)
      - Floor Speech (1 Minute)-Deficit Reduction, 1994 July 14 (Box CPM-1)
      - Floor Remarks-Opposition to Burton Amendment-CJS Bill, 1994 June 27 (Box CPM-1)
      - Floor Remarks-Transportation Appropriations, 1994 June 16 (Box CPM-1)
      - Floor (1 Minute)-Marxists in the House (Nay-sayers), 1994 June 16 (Box CPM-1)
      - Remarks-The Art of Building in N.C., quoted in National Building Museum Journal, 1994 Summer (Box CPM-1)
      - Remarks to UNISPHERE International Ventures Forum-RTP [Research Triangle Park], 1994 May 31 (Box CPM-1)
      - Remarks-RDU-London Route Inauguration, 1994 May 26 (Box CPM-1)
      - Remarks-Groundbreaking for Sedgewood Apartments-DHIC [Downtown Housing Improvement Corporation] (Raleigh), 1994 May 23 (Box CPM-1)
      - CR-Crime Field Hearing, 1994 May 20 (Box CPM-1)
      - Art of Building in N.C., 1994 May 16 (Box CPM-1)
      - Speech-Commencement Address, Milligan College, 1994 May 15 (Box CPM-1)
      - National Stone Association Speech, 1994 May 10 (Box CPM-1)
      - Statement-N.C. JOBLINKS Grant Announcement-Wake Technical Community College, 1994 May 9 (Box CPM-1)
      - Statement-Falls Lake, 1994 Apr. 29 (Box CPM-1)
      - The Vote in South Africa, 1994 Apr. 28 (Box CPM-1)
      - Chapel Hill Bicentennial, 1994 Apr. 24 (Box CPM-1)
      - Speech-Pollution Prevention-N.C. Chemical and Pharmaceutical Industry, NCSU-Closing Remarks, 1994 Apr. 22 (Box CPM-1)
      - Statement-Grant Announcement for N.C. Housing Finance Agency, 1994 Apr. 8 (Box CPM-1)
      - Talking Points-People for the American Way, Speech, 1994 Apr. 6 (Box CPM-1)
      - DLC [Democratic Leadership Council] Article, 1994 Apr. (Box CPM-1)
      - Balanced Budget Amendment (3 Statements), 1994 Mar. 16-1994 Mar. 17 (Box CPM-1)
      - FY 1995 Budget Resolution (2 Statements: Kasich, Con; Sabo [?], Pro), 1994 Mar. 10 (Box CPM-1)
      - Farm Breakfast Remarks, 1994 Mar. 5 (Box CPM-1)
      - Senate Committee on Foreign Relations re: Jeanette Hyde, 1994 Feb. 25 (Box CPM-1)
      - Strengthening the Black Family, Inc., Floor Statement, 1994 Feb. 23 (Box CPM-1)
      - Dedication of Cornerstone (Homelessness), 1994 Feb. 21 (Box CPM-1)
      - Fourth District Health Care Forum, 1994 Feb. 11 (Box CPM-1)
      - Statement Before Senate Committee on Environment and Public Works re: Jesse L. White, Jr., 1994 Feb. 4 (Box CPM-1)
      - Health Care Forum, 1994 Feb. 3 (Box CPM-1)
      - Remarks on Crime Bill, 1993 Nov. 29 (Box CPM-1)
      - Penny-Kasich Amendment, 1993 Nov. 23 (Box CPM-1)
      - Debate-Floor Statement on Penny-Kasich Amendment, 1993 Nov. 22 (Box CPM-1)
      - NAFTA Floor Statement, 1993 Nov. 17 (Box CPM-1)
      - UNC Clinical Research Video Introduction: Verne S. Caviness General Clinic Research Center, 1993 Nov. 15 (Box CPM-1)
      - Newsletter-Reports from Washington, 1993 Nov. 12 (Box CPM-1)
      - Franklin County Airport Grand Opening, 1993 Nov. 10 (Box CPM-1)
      - Speech-NCSU-Wood Machining and Tooling Grant Announcement, 1993 Nov. 1 (Box CPM-1)
      - Article-Access to Economic Security-Community Transportation Reporter, 1993 Nov. (Box CPM-1)
      - N.C. Special Olympics Equestrian Championships, 1993 Oct. 30 (Box CPM-1)
      - House Floor Debate-Final Passage of Transportation Appropriations Bill, 1993 Oct. 21 (Box CPM-1)
      - House Floor Debate-Final Passage of CJS Appropriations Bill: National Endowment for Democracy (NED), 1993 Oct. 20 (Box CPM-1)
      - CJS Appropriations, 1993 Oct. 19 (Box CPM-1)
      - Op-Ed Piece-JOBLINKS Initiative Community Transportation Newsletter, 1993 Oct. 14 (Box CPM-1)
      - London Gateway Rally, 1993 Oct. 4 (Box CPM-1)
      - UNC [University of North Carolina] Cystic Fibrosis Grant Announcement, 1993 Oct. 4 (Box CPM-1)
      - Transportation Appropriations Floor Debate, 1993 Sept. 22 (Box CPM-1)
      - Srs. [Seniors] Housing Conference, 1993 Sept. 17 (Box CPM-1)
      - National Institute of Environmental Health Sciences-Speech, 1993 Sept. 13 (Box CPM-1)
      - Commencement Address-Wake Tech, 1993 Aug. 20 (Box CPM-1)
      - Health Care Financial Management Association-Myrtle Beach, 1993 Aug. 11 (Box CPM-1)
      - One-minute Floor Speech, "Now Is the Time," 1993 Aug. 5 (Box CPM-1)
      - Budget Reconciliation Debate-FY '94, 1993 Aug. 5 (Box CPM-1)
      - Tribute to Rep. Paul Henry, circa 1993 Aug. 3 (Box CPM-1)
      - Small Business Needs the Economic Plan, 1-Minute Floor Speech, 1993 July 30 (Box CPM-1)
      - Special Order-Earned Income Tax Credit, 1993 July 29 (Box CPM-1)
      - In Memory of Thad Eure-Extension of Remarks, 1993 July 26 (Box CPM-1)
      - What We Must Do, Budget Conference 1-Minute Floor Speech, 1993 July 21 (Box CPM-1)
      - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency] Consolidation in RTP- Charlotte Observer, 1993 July 19 (Box CPM-1)
      - House Judiciary Subcommittee on Immigration Testimony re: Charlie Tsui, 1993 July 15 (Box CPM-1)
      - 1-Minute Floor Speech-Local Benefits of Economic Plan, 1993 June 17 (Box CPM-1)
      - NAPMW [National Association of Professional Mortgage Women], 1993 June 7 (Box CPM-1)
      - Speech-Baccalaureate Address at Northwood High School, 1993 June 6 (Box CPM-1)
      - Speech-Baccalaureate Address at St. Mary's, 1993 June 5 (Box CPM-1)
      - Confirmation of Michael A. Stegman, 1993 May 24 (Box CPM-1)
      - 1-Minute Floor Speech-Budget Reconciliation, 1993 May 20 (Box CPM-1)
      - Endangered Species Act-Statement to Charlotte Observer, 1993 May 7 (Box CPM-1)
      - 1-Minute Speech-Only a Bump in the Road-Impact of Not Passing Stimulus Package, 1993 May 6 (Box CPM-2)